mytemplatestorage.com 2019-06-23

# Privacy policy - MyTemplateStorage

_Effective date May 25, 2018_

We have created this MyTemplateStorage privacy policy to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy of our affiliate partners. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy and how we handle the personal information collected from our affiliates.

## What This Privacy Policy Covers

This privacy policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information collected by us through a website owned and operated by us. This privacy policy does not apply to the practices of companies that are not in our direct subjection, or of persons not employed by us, including any third-party content contributors bound by contract and any third-party websites to which our websites may link.

## Collection and Use of Personal Information

You may visit our websites without disclosing any personal information. However, we need certain personal information if you wish to purchase our products, register an Affiliate Account, receive our newsletter, or use certain services. If and where required, this information may include your contact information and/or your company contact information. We will use this information to reply to your inquiries, to provide you with requested products and services, to set up your member’s account, and to contact you regarding new products and services. By accessing our services and voluntarily providing us with the requested personal information, you consent to the collection and use of information in accordance with this privacy policy.

## **Children’s privacy**

Children under 13 years old are not intended to use Templatemonster.com websites, blogs and services. Their personal  information cannot be provided to or on our websites or collected for them. You may not use any of our sites, make purchases from our marketplace, leave comments in our blog and social media posts, or provide the personal information including your name, address, email and phone number if you are under 13. In case this term is violated we preserve the right to terminate your account and delete the information. In case your child’s information could be provided to us as you believe, please, email us at [privacy@templatemonster.com](mailto:privacy@templatemonster.com).

## Routine Erasure and Personal Data Blocking

The personal data shall be processed and stored by the information controller only as long as it is necessary for the  storage purpose or as far as this is granted by the European legislator or other legislators the controller is subject to.

In case of the expiration of the storage period granted by the European legislator or another competent legislator or the storage purpose being inapplicable TemplateMonster.com will erase or block the personal data.

## Collection and Use of Non-personal Information

We automatically receive and record certain types of non-personal information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, the page you requested and cookie information.

Cookies are used by TemplateMonster.com and all its partner sites to get the users demographic and behavior information. Cookie is a file placed on a device when a website is visited. Its use can be eliminated using the browser settings; however, disabling them limits some features on our main site as well as makes impossible tracking the affiliate link sale for the affiliate account.

Please, refer to our [cookies policy](https://www.templatemonster.com/cookie-policy.php) for more information about the functional and analytical cookies we use.

We may this information to customize the advertising and content you see and to fulfill your requests for certain products and services. However, we do not connect these non-personal data to any personal information collected from you. We also allow third party companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. These cookies are not connected to any personal information in any way. Third party cookie usage is subject to their own privacy policies, and we assume no responsibility or liability for their use.

## Google Analytics

All your customers activity data within TemplateMonster.com site are collected by us using Google Analytics by Google, Inc. (“Google”). This software analyzes users behavior using cookies; it collects cookies and stores them on Google servers in the United States. These data are used by Google to evaluate the users behavior in general, to provide the site managers with reports and send data to services connected with website activity and Internet usage.

Where required to do so by law or where the information is processed by third parties on behalf of Google the data may be transferred by Google to third parties.

Your IP address will NOT be associated by Google with any other data held by Google. Cookies can be blocked in case you do not want to provide your browsing data to Google.

More information on Google Analytics can be checked on [Google analytics opt-out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en), [www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/), [www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html](http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html) and [www.google.com/analytics/](https://www.google.com/analytics/).

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

We may disclose your personal information to third parties who work on our behalf to provide products and services requested by you. We may share personal information for these purposes only with third parties whose privacy policies are consistent with ours or who agree to abide by our policies with respect to personal information. We may otherwise disclose your personal information when:

We have your express consent to share the information for a specified purpose;

We need to respond to subpoenas, court orders or such other legal process;

We need to protect the personal safety of the users of our websites or defend the rights or property that pertain to us;

We find that your actions on our websites violate our Terms of Use document or any of our usage guidelines pertaining to corresponding products or services.

## Consent

If you do not consent to the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information as outlined in this policy, please do not provide any personal information to us. If you have provided personal information to us and cease to consent to its use or disclosure as outlined herein, please notify us at support@mytemplatestorage.com.

## Security

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be considered 100% secure. However, your information stored with us is protected for your privacy and security. In the high security areas of our websites, as identified on the site, we use industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions. We also safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access, through access control procedures, network firewalls and physical security measures. Further, we retain your personal information only as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes identified above or as required by governing law.

## Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may at any time, without notice to you and in its sole discretion, amend this policy from time to time. Please review this policy periodically. Your continued use of our websites after any such amendments signifies your acceptance thereof.

## Questions and Suggestions

If you have questions or suggestions about this privacy policy, or your own personal information, please e-mail us at support@mytemplatestorage.com.
